你们可能已经注意到了，Claude 给 Claude 应用增加了一个新功能。坦白说，我认为这是他们今年推出的最棒的更新之一。
You might have already noticed, but Claude just added a new feature to the Claude app. And I'm going to be honest with you, I think this is one of the best updates they've shipped all year.
这个新功能叫作 Claude Code Projects，它的功能比名字听起来要酷得多。
And this new feature is called Claude Code Projects, and it's way cooler than the name makes it sound.
过去 48 小时里，我一直在用这个新功能。
And I've been using this new feature for the past 48 hours straight.
我真心希望 OpenAI 能在 Codex 里推出一模一样的功能，因为它真的非常出色。
And I genuinely hope OpenAI releases the same exact feature inside Codex because it's simply that good.
现在，这可不是那个已经存在好几年的旧版 Claude Projects 功能。
Now, this is not the old Claude Projects feature that's been around for a couple of years.
你可以把这个版本的 Claude Code Projects 理解为一个有组织的智能体编排器。
You can think of this version of Claude Code Projects as an organized agent orchestrator.
要理解它，你只需要看一眼就行了。
And in order to understand it, you just need to see it.
现在我们进入 Claude 桌面端应用。
So here we are in the Claude Desktop app.
我们要聊的这个全新的功能，是他们更新后的 projects 功能。
And the feature we're talking about today, which is brand new, is their updated projects feature.
在下面你可以看到这三个图标。
And down here you'll see these three icons.
这是我在过去 24 小时内创建的三个用于业务的项目，其中有两个正在运行。
Here are my three projects that I've created over the last 24 hours that I use for my business, two of which are working.
我有一个项目是做长篇内容，另一个是用来全方位管理我的智能体原生网站。
I have one project for long form content and one to fully manage my agent native website.
如果我们点击进入我的站点管理器项目，你可以看到我的智能体正在工作。
If we click into my site manager project, you can see that my agent is working.
如何给它提供访问网站的权限。
How to give access to the site.
但你会注意到这里其实并不是在运行。
But you will notice here that it's actually not working here.
它是在这里的这个线程里运行的。
It's working in a thread right here.
Project 的作用是把你的主编排器智能体与其中的线程分开。
What projects does is it separates your main orchestrator agent from the threads within it.
我们以长篇内容专家作为例子。
Let's look at the long form expert as an example here.
目前，我的智能体正在处理 Meta Muse 文章，但这只是编排器智能体。
Right now, my agent is working on Meta Muse article, but this is just the orchestrator agent.
为了看到实际进行工作的线程，我要点这里，这个线程就是工作发生的地方。
In order to see the thread where this work is actually happening, I'm going to click here and this thread right here is where the work is happening.
这就是搭载 Opus 3.5 的 Claude 在为创作这篇 Meta Muse 文章而工作的地方。
This is where Claude with Opus 5 is doing the work to create this MetaMuse article.
现在，如果我们点击“线程”，我们就能看到这个编排器智能体创建的所有线程。
Now, if we click on threads, here we can see all of the threads that this orchestrator agent has created.
我想再写一篇关于我如何使用 Composio 来集中存储
I want to create another article on how I'm using Composio to centrally store
我的技能，以便我能将它们与 Muse、Claude、Code、Codex 和 Grokbot 一起使用。
my skills so that I can use them with Muse, Claude, Code, Codex, and Grokbot.
创建一个包含带图表文章技能的新线程。
Make a new thread that uses the article with diagrams skill.
于是我把这个提示词发给了我的长篇内容专家。
And so I just sent this prompt to my long form expert.
这是项目的名称，你可以看到它刚刚创建了这个 Composio Skills 文章线程，而且你能看到其中一个正在运行。
This is the name of the project, and you can see here it just created this Composio Skills article thread, and you can see one of which is working.
如果我们点这里，就能看到发送给这个子智能体的提示词，他们称之为“线程”。
If we click on this right here, we can see the prompt that was sent to this subagent, which they call threads.
我们有一个正在运行的线程，正在创建这个 Composio 技能文章，还有一个在等待我的指令。
We have one thread that is working, which is creating this Composio skills article, and we also have one that's waiting on me.
这一个被阻塞了。
This one is blocked.
好了，Composio 技能文章已经完成了。
Okay, the Composio skills article is done.
我在 Longform Expert 项目中询问了我的主智能体。
I asked my main agent in the Longform Expert project.
它创建了这个技能文章线程，并在该线程中生成了这个产物。
It created this skills article thread, and within this thread, it generated this artifact.
就在这里。
And here it is.
每个智能体一个技能。
One skill every agent.
这是一个我很喜欢用的技能，用来梳理任何想法，让我能直观地了解它们是如何结合在一起的。我是个视觉型的人，这就是我喜欢这个技能的原因。
And so this is just a skill that I love to use to outline any idea so that I'm able to get a grasp of how it all visually works together. I'm very visual, and that's why I really like this skill.
而且和这个能够委派任务并创建各种不同线程的智能体合作非常有趣。
And it's really fun to work with this agent that can delegate and create all of these different threads.
在接下来的视频中，我们将深入探讨 Claude Projects，并全面涵盖相关内容。
For the rest of this video, we're going to be diving deep into Claude Projects, and we're going to cover it all.
我们先从初步演示开始，看看如何创建一个新项目以及相关的基础操作。
We're going to start off with an initial demo of actually how to start a new project and the basics of doing that.
然后我们将讨论关于 Claude Projects 的七个关键点，以便你能将其应用到你的业务中。
Then we're going to talk about the seven things that you need to know about Claude Projects so that you can apply it to your business.
接着，我们将在创建的项目中实际操作一些非常酷的工作流。
And then we're actually going to do work inside the project that we create and do some really cool workflows.
好，那我们现在就开始创建我们的第一个项目。
Okay, so let's go ahead and create our first project.
我正在使用 Claude 桌面端应用，点击加号就可以创建一个新项目。
And I'm on the Claude Desktop app, and I can hit plus to create a new project.
这个项目将命名为 Shortform Plus Twitter。
This is going to be called Shortform Plus Twitter.
我的目标是为这个项目设定一个目标，因为这能为这个特定项目确定重点。
And my goal for the project, and I always set a goal for the project because it kind of sets the focus for this specific project.
这里我将填入：帮助我（里利·布朗）在 Instagram、TikTok、Twitter 上增长。
Here I'm going to put to help me, parentheses Riley Brown, grow on Instagram, TikTok, Twitter,
线程，并且我还会加入相关的链接。
threads, and I'm just gonna include linked
放进去。
in.
现在我们可以添加上下文。
Now we could add context.
我们现在不需要做这个。
We don't need to do that now.
我们可以稍后再做，现在我们先创建项目。
We can do that later, and we're just going to create the project.
你会注意到，每当你创建一个这样的项目——这是一个新的 Claude 项目时，
You'll notice here, whenever you create one of these projects, and this is a new Claude project.
你就会看到它出现在左侧。
You'll see it pop up over here on the left side.
并且它会被固定在顶部。
And it is kind of pinned to the top.
你可以非常方便地在上方更改项目的名称，也可以更改它的外观。
You can change the name of your project very easily right up here. And you can also change what it looks like.
我要选一个符合这种感觉的图标。我觉得这个心形加上看起来有点像 Instagram 的图标不错。
And I'm going to pick an icon that kind of matches this vibe. I think this heart plus something that kind of looks like Instagram.
现在我们创建了一个新项目，除了我的长内容、我的网站管理器。这只是我用来熟悉平台的通用智能体。
So now we have a new project created along with my long form, my site manager. And this is kind of just a general agent that I was using to kind of learn the platform.
现在我要说：创建两个新线程。
So now I'm going to just say create two new threads.
然后我接着说：其中一个，对里利·布朗在 Instagram 上表现最好的短视频内容进行深入研究。
And then I'm just going to say one, uh, do some in-depth research on Riley Brown regarding his best performing short
使用 Scrape Creators 获取他排名前 15 的视频转录。确保它们不是赞助视频，这样我们就能查看他最优质的原创视频。
form content on Instagram. Use Scrape Creators to get the transcripts for his top 15. Make sure they're ones that are not sponsored videos so that we can look at his best organic videos.
然后我希望你研究一下创作短视频的最佳脚本方法，并对短视频领域进行一些深入调研。
Then I want you to look into the best ways to script short form videos and just do some in-depth research in general on short
包括当下制作短内容的一些现代策略。
the modern strategies of short form content creation.
这样我们就可以让智能体去执行了，
So we can fire this off in our agent,
我们的智能体会在这里开启两个新线程。
and our agent is going to spin up two new threads here.
好了，搞定。它刚刚在这里启动了两个线程。
Okay, there you go. It just spun up two threads here.
如果这个被折叠了，我们很容易就能把这个线程打开。
And so if this was closed, we can very easily open up this thread.
我们也可以打开这个线程，你可以看到所有的线程都在这儿。因为它们刚开始，所以都在运行中。
We can also open up this thread, and you can see all of the threads right here. And since they both just started, they're both working.
现在我们有了这个项目。
So now we have this project.
它的核心围绕一个共同目标：增加我的短视频和 Twitter 影响力。
It's organized around a common goal, which is to grow my short form and Twitter.
我可以与这个智能体交互，它能开启线程，然后这些线程去执行具体的工作。
I can interact with this agent, and this agent can spin up threads, and then these threads can actually do the work.
这两个线程都创建好了，并且在各自的线程中完成了工作。
And so both of those threads were created and they are done working within the threads.
我可以看到每一个任务最后都生成了一个产物。
And so I can see that each one of these actually ended with an artifact.
这些都是我的热门视频，以及我最火的 Instagram 帖子的视频文稿。
And so these are all of the top videos and the transcripts of my videos for my top Instagram posts.
看，这两个都已经完成了。
And here you go. You can see that both of them are done.
当你打开一个线程时，你看，如果我们打开这个线程，它创建了这个产物。
When you open a thread, right, you can see here, like if we just open this thread, it created this artifact.
你现在可以打开所有的产物，并且可以通过打字直接在这里编辑产物，或者在特定部分留下评论，这就是你
All artifacts you can now open up, and you can actually edit the artifact directly here by typing, or you can actually leave a comment on a specific part, and that's how you
编辑这些产物有多方便。
how easy it is to edit these artifacts.
我们创建了一个新项目，对吧？我们设定了目标，完成了初始设置，与主智能体进行了沟通，然后它分派给了子智能体。
So we've created a new project, right? We set a goal, we went through the initial setup, we talked to our main agent that then delegated to subagents.
现在让我们来看看一些问题和其他你应该了解的内容。
Now let's go over some questions and other things that you should know.
这是一个新的项目功能。
So this is a new projects feature.
它到底是什么？
What exactly is it?
这是我对 Claude Projects 的理解。
So here's how I think of Claude Projects.
我甚至给它起了一个替代名称，叫 FFOAO，也就是“有组织的智能体编排文件夹”。
And I actually gave it an alternative name, which is a FFOAO or a folder for organized agent orchestration.
当你创建一个项目时（就像我们做的这个“短视频+Twitter”），它会创建一个文件夹，层级结构的最顶端是你的
When you create a project, which we did, short form plus Twitter, it creates this folder, and the kind of the top of the hierarchy is your
与这个能够开启其他对话的智能体的交流。
chatting with this agent that can spin up other chats.
你创建的每个项目都像这样一个文件夹。在这个项目里，你只有一个对话或者一个主智能体，它可以派生出许多不同的线程。
Every project that you create is kind of like this folder. And within this project, you only have one chat or one main agent that can spin up many different threads.
而在整个文件夹中，它们都共享相同的记忆、产物和常规操作。
And then within this entire folder, they all contain the same memory, artifacts, and routines.
如你所见，我们现在在“短视频+Twitter”项目里，对吧？这就像是一个带有名字的文件夹。
As you can see here, we are in the short form plus Twitter project, right? Which is kind of like a folder with a name.
这里只有一个对话。
There's only one chat.
你可以看到这里所有的会话。你可以创建任意数量的会话或线程。
And you can see here we have all of the sessions. You can create as many sessions or threads as you want.
还有一个包含所有制品的库，任何创建的文件都会保留在这个面板里。
There's also a library which has all the artifacts, and any files that get created stay in this pane right here.
所以它包含了这些制品。
So it has these artifacts.
而且正如我们稍后会提到的，它还有存在于项目内部而非在外部全局运行的常规操作，就在这个计划标签页里。
And then also, as we'll get to later, it has routines that live within the project rather than living outside of the project and operate globally in this scheduled tab.
它们现在都在项目内部了，这是全新的功能。
They now live within the project, which is completely new.
所以如果非要总结一两点的话，这个新的 Projects 功能就是一个用于组织智能体编排的文件夹。
So if there's one takeaway here, this new projects feature is just a folder for organized agent orchestration.
那么关于这个新 Project 功能，你需要了解的第二点是它与之前的项目功能不同。
And so the second thing that you need to understand about this new projects feature is it's different than the previous projects feature.
在我看来，旧版的 Claude 项目功能几乎没什么用。
The old Claude projects feature was kind of useless, in my opinion.
这也是为什么我在这个新项目功能推出前，上一个创建的项目是在 2024 年。
And that's actually why my next most recent project that I've created before this new projects feature was in 2024.
它叫作“调试”。
it's called debugging.
这就是它当时的样貌。
And this is actually what it looked like.
它仅仅是一个带有系统指令和实际上下文的聊天文件夹，对吧？你可以上传文件。
All it was was a folder of chats with a system instructions and actually context, right? You could upload files.
我觉得 ChatGPT 也稍微模仿了这个功能，但同样，我认为它也挺没用的，对吧？你可以在这里上传文件，它有记忆，你还可以添加指令。
And ChatGPT, I think, copied this feature a little bit, but again, I think it was relatively useless, right? You could upload files here, it had memory, and you could also add instructions.
它基本上就像是一个可以在 Claude 里使用的聊天文件夹。
And it was basically just like a folder of chats that you could use inside Claude.
但现在的这个项目并不是那样的。
That is not what this project is.
它的深度远超于此。
This is much deeper than that.
在进入 Claude 项目能做的那些有趣功能之前，我想先谈谈一个你需要注意的事情。
So before we get to all of the fun things that Claude projects can do, I want to talk about something that you need to be aware of.
那就是 Token 成本。
And that is token cost.
对于那些试用过 Claude 3.5 或 Claude 3.5 的朋友，你们知道这些模型有多贵。
For those of you who've tried Astra or Fable 5.1, you know how expensive these models can be.
如果你点击这个小按钮，你就能看到你的五小时限制，对吧？一旦达到五小时限制，他们就会切断你的连接。
And if you click on this little button right here, you can actually see your five hour limit, right? Once you reach the five hour limit, they will cut you off.
还有一个周限制，还有一个 Fable 的周限制。
There's also a weekly limit, and then there's a weekly fable limit.
你还有备用的使用额度，如果你达到了任何限制时可以使用这些额度。
And then you have your backup usage credits that you can use if you hit any of your limits.
而且由于 Claude Projects 是一个智能体编排器，这意味着你有一个可以启动许多不同聊天的智能体，而所有这些
And since Claude Projects is an agent orchestrator, meaning you have an agent that can spin up many different chats, all of which
都使用不同的模型，对吧？
use different models, right?
这个对话正在使用 Claude 3.5，这非常昂贵。
This chat right here is using Fable 5.1, which is really expensive.
你可以想象一下，如果你的智能体启动了三个或四个不同的聊天会话，Token 的消耗会迅速堆积。
And you can imagine if your agent is spinning up three or four different chat sessions, the token usage can add up very quickly.
但他们增加了一个很酷的功能，如果你想节省 Token，可以点击这个小使用按钮，然后查看完整的
But one thing they added that's really cool if you want to conserve tokens is you can press this little usage button right here, and you can see see full
项目使用情况。
project usage.
这会给你提供项目的完整明细，对吧？
And this gives you the full breakdown of the project, right?
我们有一个正在互动的智能体对话，而那个智能体启动了七个不同的线程。
We have one agent chat session that we're messaging, and that agent has spun up seven different threads.
总共是 8710 万个 Token。
Total 87.1 million tokens.
你可以看到这里，协调器占了17%。
And you can see here that the coordinator 17%.
就是这样。
And there you go.
我们可以看到按线程划分的所有明细。
We can see all of it broken down by thread.
这个线程消耗的 token 最多。
This thread used the most tokens.
点击这里，它会直接带我们进入那个线程。
And here, if we click on this, it takes us directly to the thread.
你可以看到我们实际上创建了很多内容。
And you can see here we've actually created a lot.
我们在这里创建了这个项目，我问了它很多不同的问题。
We created this project here, and I've asked it a ton of different questions.
我们创建了一些技能，这就是为什么这个线程消耗更多。
We've created a few skills, and that's why this one has taken more usage.
因为正如你看到的，它有 2870 万个 token。
Because as you can see here, it has 28.7 million tokens.
很酷的是，你实际上可以看到这个线程正在使用的模型。
And what's cool is you can actually see the model that this one's using.
所以这个用的是 Fable，而这些全都在用 Opus。
So this one's using Fable, and all of these are using Opus.
所以当你开始使用 Claude Project 时，一定要留意这个，你可以追踪哪些类型的线程或 Claude 使用场景消耗了最多的 token。
So this is something that as you start using Claude Projects, definitely keep an eye on this, and you can actually keep track of what types of threads or use cases of Claude take up the most tokens.
说到大量消耗 token，我想聊聊 Claude Project 中最酷的功能，它确实挺耗 token 的，那就是设计模式。
And speaking of using a lot of tokens, I want to talk about the coolest feature of Claude Projects, which does use a lot of tokens, and that is design mode.
以前设计模式是一个隐藏得比较深的功能。如果你去 web 端点击更多并选择设计，你就可以创建一些设计。
And so design mode used to be this little tucked-away feature. If you go over to more on the web app and you click design, you could create designs.
你可以制作幻灯片、移动端应用设计、在代码库中进行设计，甚至可以创建一个设计系统。
You could create slides, mobile app designs, design in a code base, you could create a design system.
这是一个非常酷的功能，但之前被低估了。
And this is a really cool feature that was pretty underrated.
但正如你在这里看到的，在我的 智能体 原生网站的站点管理器项目中，我让它做了一次重新设计，对吧？
But as you can see here, in my site manager project for my agent native site, I had it make a redesign, right?
所以我想让它做一个新设计，我说：新建一个线程，看看我们能怎么把 claw 设计重做，提一些更好的建议。
So I wanted it to create a redesign and I said, make a new thread and figure out what we can do to redesign uh claw design to propose something better.
我基本上是想让它按照 Japandi 风格来做。
And I basically wanted it to do it in the style of Japandi.
Japandi 就是这种风格，然后它创建了这个线程，并为我的网站做了一个新设计。
So Japandi is this style, and it created this thread, and then it made a redesign of my site.
而且它不是给我一个产物的链接，而是直接在 Claude Project 里生成了它。
And rather than giving me a link to an artifact, it just created it in Claude Design.
看这个。
Look at this.
这基本上就是 Figma，对吧？我们可以在这里看到这个画布。
This is basically Figma, right? We have this board that I can look at here.
而且我实际上可以对它进行编辑。
And I can actually make edits to it.
就像 Figma 一样，这是一个画布，我可以参考它们，它给所有元素命名了，我可以点到这里，选中这个，把颜色改成白色。
And so just like Figma, it's this board, I can reference them, it names all of them, and I can come down here and I can select this and I could change this color to white.
我不喜欢那个颜色。
I actually don't like that.
我可以非常轻松地对这个进行修改。
I can very easily make changes to this.
所以我可以说：嘿，在手机视图的浅色模式下，我觉得设计画布上的字体不好看。
So I can very say, I can say, hey, on the phone view, on light mode, I just don't think the font looks good on the design board.
你不仅可以要求它为你创建这些设计画布并进行编辑，你还可以直接在项目里要求你的 AI
Not only can you ask it to create these design boards for you and edit them, you can ask your AI directly in projects
去修改它提供给你的画布。
to edit the board that it gives you.
搞定。我本来想让它做成 Japandi 风格，但你可以看到它做了一些修改。
And there you go. And I did want it to be Japan-D style, but you can see that it made some edits.
记住，我可以用这种评论功能。
And remember, I can do this like comment thing.
其实我不是这个功能的铁粉。
I actually don't not the biggest fan of this.
再改一个地方。
Make one more change.
让它酷一点。
Make it cooler.
我不喜欢这种圆形的氛围。
I don't like this circle vibe.
瞧，我可以直接把它发给 Claude。这里显示是评论。
And look at that. I can send that straight to Claude. And here it said comment.
它确实正在发送给 Claude。
It's actually sending it to Claude.
现在 Claude 正在处理这个。
And now Claude is working on this.
你可以直接在画布上看到动画，这非常酷。而且你可以同时做多件事。
And you kind of see the animation directly on the board right here, which is really cool. And you can do multiple things at once.
我可以到这里来，说这一块应该和字幕一起居中。我也可以发送这个提示词。现在有两个评论，它应该会把这两处都改了。
I could come here, I could say this should be centered along with the subtitle. And I can fire that prompt as well. And now there's two comments and it should make both of those changes.
记住，你可以在手机上的 Claude 应用里访问所有这些内容。
And remember, you can access this all from your phone on the Claud app.
所以你可以看到这里已经完成画布编辑了。
And so you can see here it is done with the board edits.
我确实可以在手机上打开它们。
And I can actually open them on my phone.
如你所见，如果我点返回，就能看到整个画布。
As you can see here, if I hit back, I can see the entire board.
然后我可以直接点击这个主设计。
And then I can click directly on this home design.
搞定。
And here you go.
这就是这里的移动端设计。
It is the mobile design right here.
我们可以填充它
We can either fill
或者我可以向下滚动，也可以把它缩放。
and I can scroll down on it, or I can fit it.
这其实做得相当扎实。
This is actually pretty solid.
这就是设计模式。
And so that is design mode.
设计模式以前是 Claude 的一个独立功能，现在它只是一个你可以使用的产物。
Design mode used to be this separate feature of Claude, and now it is simply an artifact that you can use.
这引出了关于 Claude 项目的下一个要点：你可以创建多种不同类型的产物。
So that brings me to the next thing that you need to know about Claude projects, are that you can create so many different types of artifacts.
所以如果你在你的项目中，对吧，我们创建了这个长表单专家项目，我们可以看到所有的对话，然后点击产物，
And so if you are in your project, right, we've created this long form expert project, and we see all of our chats, and we click artifacts,
或者准确点说是库，我们可以看到这个叫作产物的下拉菜单。
or actually it's called library, we can see this drop-down called artifacts.
然后我们能看到所有这些的名称。
And then we see the name for all of them.
所以在今天的对话中，我创建了 1、2、3、4、5、6、7、8 个这样的产物。
And so in this chat session today, I've created one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight of these artifacts.
要打开这些中的任何一个，我可以点击这个
And to open any of these artifacts, I can click on this
它就会真的打开出来。
and it will actually open it up.
而且我可以非常轻松地编辑这里的这个产物。
And I can very easily edit this artifact right here.
所以这一个就是一个像网页一样的产物。
And so this one is an artifact like a web page.
每当你创建一个产物时，对，这些都是带有链接的产物。
And whenever you create an artifact, right, these are artifacts with a link.
你可以到这里点击分享，我可以邀请其他人，或者让任何拥有链接的人都能查看。
You can come up here and press share, and I can invite people, or I could make this available with anyone with the link.
所以我可以公开分享它，然后复制这个链接发给任何人。
So I can share this publicly, and then I can copy this link and send it to anyone.
如果你不想要这种看起来更像网页的产物，你实际上可以要求：
And if you don't want it as an artifact, which looks more like a web page, you can actually just say, "Please, can you turn this into a
“请把它变成一个我可以编辑的幻灯片演示文稿？”
slide deck that I can edit?
“给这个添加图片，在网上找一些 Logo 来包含进去，让视觉效果更好。”
add images to this, find them on the internet for logos to include to make graphics better,
然后它就能创建一个也会显示在那个库里的幻灯片演示文稿。
And then it can create a slide deck that will also show up in that library.
你看，搞定了，我们可以把它打开。这和网页产物不同。
And there you go, it is done, and we can open this up. And this is different than the web artifacts.
这是一个幻灯片演示文稿。
This is a slide deck.
你可以看到这里我们有这些不同的幻灯片，它会自动去寻找并放入所有这些的 Logo，我非常欣赏这一点。我觉得这真的很酷。
And you can see here we have these different slides, and it went out and found the logos for all of these and placed it in, which I really appreciate. I think that's really cool.
你可以创建幻灯片演示文稿、文档、电子表格，所有这些类型的东西。
You can create slide decks, documents, spreadsheets, all those types of things.
所以我想谈论的是关于 Claude Projects 你需要了解的第六点，就是它的 iOS 应用体验非常棒，网页端也是一样。
So what I want to talk about is the sixth thing that you need to understand about Claude Projects, is that its iOS app works amazing, and so does its web app.
这就是你们可能已经见过的 Claude 应用。
So here's the Claude app that you guys have probably have already seen.
这看起来很熟悉，但如果你点击这个返回按钮，然后按下左上角的这个按钮，你就能看到我们可以访问 Claude Code 和 Claude Projects。
This looks very familiar, but if you hit this back button and then you press this top left button, here you can see that we have access to Cloud Code and then Claude Projects.
在这里，就像在桌面端一样，对吧，你可以看到这里所有的置顶项目，和 iOS 应用一模一样。
And here, just like on the desktop app, right, you see all of these pinned projects right here, same as the iOS app.
我刚才正在处理我的长篇导出项目。
So I was just working in my long form export project.
我可以打开它，通过点击这个按钮，你可以查看所有的线程。
So I can open this up and you can view all of your threads by pressing this button right here.
我们刚刚在为 Composio 写这篇文章，并且我让它创建了一个幻灯片演示文稿。
And we were just working on this article for Composio, and I had it create a slide deck.
现在我可以在手机上打开它，就像你在这里看到的。
Now I can open it on my phone, as you can see right here.
我可以翻到下一页，可以放大，可以看到幻灯片的样式，这真的很酷。
And I can go to the next page, I can zoom in, I can see how the slide looks, which is really cool.
注意这里，我们正处于 11 页中的第 3 页。
Notice here that we're on slide three of 11.
那我该如何最方便地进行修改？我能做的一件事是点击这个按钮，然后在第三页添加一条评论，让这个幻灯片
And how would I make an edit most easily? So one thing I can do to make an edit is I could press this button right here, and I could just add a comment on slide three, make this slide
变得更好。
better.
还有另一种修改的方法，看我接下来怎么做。
One other way that you can make edits, watch what I do here.
我可以开启语音对话，然后打开幻灯片演示文稿，直接用手机把我的修改要求说出来。
I can start a voice chat and then open up the slide deck, and I can just speak my changes out loud from my phone.
这就是我走路时操作的方法。今天早上我编辑幻灯片演示文稿时就是这么做的，我只要把它打开。
So this is what I do while walking. This is what I did this morning when I was editing my slide deck is I just turn this on.
好的，我很喜欢第四页，保持原样。
Okay, I really like slide four, keep it the way it is.
幻灯片
Slide
第五页，
five,
也就是五页中的第二处修复。
which is two of five the fix.
我觉得这里可以做个更好的图表。
I think we can make a better graphic here.
我希望这个图表做得更好一点。
I want this to be a better graphic.
请把第五页做相应的修改。
Please make that change to slide number five.
第十页很棒。
Slide ten is great.
还有，第十一页有点无聊。
And then again, slide eleven is a little boring.
请按照我刚才建议的去修改。
Please make changes to the ones that I've just suggested.
我可以发出那个指令。看到没？你可以开始语音消息，在任何地方用手机打开一个产物。
I can fire that prompt. You see that? You start a voice message, open an artifact from your phone while you're anywhere.
就像那样要求做出更改。
Ask for the changes to be made just like that.
真的就这么简单。
It really is that easy.
而且在每个项目里，你还能看到库。这里是我们在这个项目中创建的所有产物。
And then again, within each project, you can also see the library. Here's all the artifacts that we've created on this in this project.
我们可以回到这里，我点一下上面的这个，就能看到上下文、目标和名称，然后进行修改。
And we can come back here and I can press this up here, and I can see the context, the goal, and the name, and I can make changes.
甚至像这样，我可以直接在手机上查看用法。
And I can even view the usage directly from my phone, as you can see here.
这就是我们要进入的领域，对吧？这是我用过最强大的智能体范式之一，而且还能直接在手机上使用，太棒了。
And so that's the world we're going into, right? This is one of the most powerful agent paradigms I've ever used, and it's available directly on the phone, which is amazing.
关于 Claude 项目我想说的最后一件事是：线程使用工具，而不是主智能体。
And so the final thing that I want to talk about regarding Claude projects is that threads use tools, not the main agent.
在整个视频中，在这个项目里，我用了很多工具，对吧？我们制作了演示文稿，它做了很多
Throughout this video, within this project, I've used a lot of tools, right? We've created presentations, it's done a lot of
不同的产物，它可以运用特定的技能。
different artifacts, it can use certain skills.
这些都会在线程中完成。
That will all happen within the thread.
这个主对话，它的作用只是把任务委派给线程中的其他智能体。
This main chat, what this is meant to do is just delegate things to other agents in the thread.
所以记住，只有一个主对话，这就是那个主对话。
And so remember, there's only one main chat, which this is the main chat.
你可以和主对话交流，也可以和线程交流。
You can talk to the main chat and you can talk to a thread.
是的，没错。
Yes and yes.
它持有项目记忆并能看到所有内容。
It holds the project memory and sees everything.
是的。
Yes.
每当你开启一个新线程时，它有自己的记忆，或者说它拥有你开始它之前那一刻为止的项目记忆，这很有意思，这就是为什么你应该把主对话
And whenever you start a new thread, it has its own memory or it has the memory of the project up until when you started it, which is very interesting, which is why you should use the main chat
当作项目经理，对吧？
as kind of the project manager, right?
它负责管理所有不同的线程。
It's managing all the different threads.
这个智能体可以启动其他线程，而如果你是在和线程内的智能体交流，它就无法开启新线程了。
This agent can start other threads, whereas if you're talking to the agent within the thread, it cannot spin up new threads.
但线程有连接器，它可以创建产物、幻灯片、电子表格等等。
But the thread has connectors, it has, it can create artifacts, slide deck spreadsheets, and more.
它可以运行代码、浏览网络、发起拉取请求，还能创建定时运行的常规操作。
It can run code, browse the web, and open pull requests, and it can create routines that run on a schedule.
而主对话就没法做这些。
Whereas the main chat can do none of those things.
所以这就是主对话和它能派生出的线程之间的区别。
And so that is kind of a summary between this main chat and then the threads that this main chat can spawn.
总而言之，我们今天讨论了这个 Projects 功能与旧版功能的不同之处，它现在更像是一个用于组织智能体编排的文件夹。
So in summary, today, we talked about how this projects feature is different than the old projects feature, in that it can be more thought of as a folder for organized agent orchestration,
每个项目都有一个单一的对话会话或主对话会话，它可以派生出比主对话拥有更多工具能力的线程。
where each project has a single chat session or a main chat session that can spin out threads that has way more tool use than the main chat.
所以所有的工作都在这里完成。
So this is all of the work is done here.
编排是由这个对话完成的，而且所有内容都存在这个文件夹里，对吧？
The orchestration is done by this chat, and all of it lives within this folder, right?
这是一个可以让这些智能体协同工作的组织良好的文件夹。
This organized folder where these agents can work together.
而且它们以一种非常有趣且新颖的方式共享记忆、产物和常规操作。
And they all share memory, artifacts, and routines in a very interesting and novel way.
所以我觉得这是 Claude 有一段时间以来发布的最棒的功能。
So I think this is the best thing that Cloud has released in a while.
记得留意 Token 的消耗情况。
Remember to be aware of token usage.
你是在并行使用这些智能体，所以如果任务简单的话，尽量用 Opus 甚至 Sonnet。
You're using these agents in parallel, so try and use Opus or even Sonnet whenever you can if it's an easy task.
记住你可以创建任何类型的产物。
Remember that you can create any type of artifact.
而且现在设计模式已经内置到 Projects 中了，这个功能被严重低估了，简直不可思议。
And now design mode is built into projects, which is so underrated, it's unbelievable.
你可以在 iOS 应用上使用它，因为这些都是云端智能体。目前还不能在项目内创建本地的 Claude Code 会话。
You can use it from your iOS app because all of these are cloud agents. You can't create local clawed code sessions within a project yet.
我听说他们很快就会加入这个功能，那会非常酷。我会再聊聊那个。
I heard they're adding that soon, which will be really cool. I'll talk about that.
然后是线程来使用工具，而不是主智能体。
And then threads use the tools, not the main agent.
工作是在线程中完成的，编排是由主智能体或者他们所说的“对话”来完成的。
The work is done in the threads, the orchestration is done by the main agent or what they call the chat.
希望这个视频能给你带来很多收获。随着我用得更多，我会做一个更深入的演示、指南和教程风格的视频。
I hope you got a ton from this video. I'm gonna do a much more in-depth demo and guide and more of a tutorial style video as I use this more.
我想在制作超长教程视频之前先用它一两周。
I wanna use this for a week or two before I make a super long tutorial video.
我还需要做更多的测试。
I have to do a lot more testing.
我的团队也会进行大量的测试。
And my team is gonna do a lot more testing as well.
我现在在我的工作室里。
I'm here in my studio.
我们马上就要……我不知道能不能挪动这个，但我们要把后面的这面墙重新刷漆。
We are about to be, I don't know if I can move this, but we're painting this wall back here.
我们正在做一些粉刷工作。
We're doing some painting.
这里将变成新的工作室，对吧？
This is gonna become the new studio, right?
我超级兴奋。
and I'm super excited.
这会很棒的。整面墙后面都会放一些酷炫的硬件项目。
It's going to be amazing. This whole wall is going to have cool hardware projects on the back.
基本上，这将成为我的智能体原生工作室。
Basically, going to be my agent native studio.
我打算在这里做大量的实验，这也是为什么我现在在这样一个有点简陋的临时工作室里，因为我正处于场地交接期，而且我们即将进入
I'm going to run a ton of experiments in here, and that's why I'm kind of in this weird makeshift studio, is because I'm in between sets and we are going to get into
在接下来的几年里，我们要搞很多有趣的东西，对吧？显然包括我最热爱、也是我最大的热情所在——AI智能体之类的东西。
all kinds of fun things over the next few years, right? Obviously, AI agents and stuff, which I love, my biggest passion.
但我现在的新爱好是硬件。我们要开始搞3D打印，搞机器人，搞智能家居设备，还有……智能眼镜，
But my new passion is hardware. We're going to get into 3D printing, we're going to get into robotics, we're going to get into smart at-home devices, we're going to get into uh smart glasses,
我们要去尝试所有这些融合了硬件和AI智能体的不同领域。
we're going to get into all of these different things that kind of blend hardware and AI agents.
我简直着迷于这两个领域的交汇点。
I'm I'm obsessed with that intersection between those two things.
这就是为什么我就在这样一个临时工作室里。
So that's why I'm in this makeshift studio.
非常感谢大家的观看。请点赞并订阅，我们即将创作出更多内容。
Thank you guys so much for watching. Please like and subscribe. We're about to create so much more content.
制作会越来越精良，效果会越来越好，也会变得更有趣。
It's going to get more polished, it's going to get better, it's going to be a lot more fun.
再次感谢大家的观看。
And thank you guys for watching.
我们下个视频再见。
I'll see you here for the next one.